It's the western death comedy champ.
[cheering]
And now your host, Martin L.
[music]
[cheering]
We're back. Yo, give my man a round of applause.\h
Kick Capri, [applause] [cheering] what's up,\h\h
man? What's up, G? How you doing?\h
Give me something, man. Cuz see,\h\h
you know what? People don't really know how bad\h
you are. So, hook something up for me. You know,\h\h
I'mma dance. Can I get a little lady to dance\h
with me? Can I get somebody there? Oh. Oh. Oh,\h\h
hold up. We'll talk after this. Um\h
uh uh go ahead. Give me something.
God, you're the bad mother. All right, give\h
him a ride. You the baddest. I'm sorry. I I\h\h
felt white there for a minute now. You wanted\h
to come up here and dance with me, but come\h\h
here. Come here. You come here. Yes. Yes. would\h
[cheering] bring that [\h__\h] Come here. Come here.
[cheering] I'm saying come here. You my sister.\h
I love you. Come here. [cheering] I'm saying\h\h
though. You I'm saying I'm saying this is my\h
friend and now you're auntie and you're telling\h\h
now. What the [\h__\h] up? I know Big Bird out of\h
business, but what the [\h__\h] [screaming] up?
[cheering]
You know you on TV now with this [\h__\h] Everybody\h\h
going to go look. There go big\h
bird y'all. They going to hone.
So your son, you got a little son. So okay to\h
what's your name? Denise. Okay. To Denise's son,\h\h
tell mama don't wear this [\h__\h]\h
outside no more. I love you. Okay, baby.
Y'all are going to stop wearing that [\h__\h]\h
to shows like this. [applause] Thank y'all\h\h
for coming out. We're here again. Hi, Mr.\h
White Man. How you doing? Every chance I get,\h\h
I kind of want to acknowledge a white\h
person, especially after the riots. I\h\h
just kind of want to I just kind of want to\h
say I have nothing against you and the people\h\h
that have courage to come to this show. We are\h
going to rise as a [\h__\h] people, aren't we?
[applause] We will rise. Cuz you know what's wild?\h
They trying to make it seem like black people was\h\h
doing all that stealing, looting and [\h__\h] I\h
ain't going to lie. I got me some [\h__\h] No. No.\h\h
But it wasn't black people that was doing\h
all that [\h__\h] It was the Mexicans. They\h\h
just didn't show that. And the Mexicans didn't\h
even know what the cause was about. They just\h\h
saw opportunity to get some free [\h__\h] Serious.\h
A Mexican came up to me. Yo, my friend. This is\h\h
[\h__\h] up. This [\h__\h] never [\h__\h] happened. The\h
way they beat Ronnie Dangerfield was [\h__\h] up.
[cheering and applause] This is far.
We going to stop this [\h__\h] man. Cuz white\h
people I knew for for years, man. My agents,\h\h
man, panic. You know, we going to get justice. My\h
white agent come up to me, Martin. Listen. Okay.\h\h
I didn't I didn't know Rodney. I didn't know\h
him. Come on. I love black people. Come on.\h\h
But that was a I was in LA when that [\h__\h]\h
happened. It was [\h__\h] was nice though cuz\h\h
white people were very nice that night. You like\h
no can I get over? Sure. God [\h__\h] All right.
Love you. [\h__\h] love you. So I'm just glad\h
to be here again. I want to welcome you guys\h\h
that came out and sorry's up there. You're\h
late and but thank you for coming anyway.\h\h
So we got a great show. So y'all just put\h
your [\h__\h] fast and your seat belts cuz\h\h
uh we gonna keep doing this. So moving on to the\h
show. This brother coming to the stage is from\h\h
Atlanta. Young brother, very funny. I know you\h
going to enjoy him. He lives in California now,\h\h
so he's doing his thing out there. Give it\h
up for Chris Tucker. [applause and music]
[music]
Pissed off, man. Just got me a new place,\h
man. Hate my neighbors, man. I got neighbors\h\h
that borrow [\h__\h] all the time. You ever had a\h
neighbor that borrow your [\h__\h] and keep it so\h\h
long? You have to borrow it back. Like, come on.\h
You got a broom I can borrow, man. No, you got my\h\h
goddamn broom. That ain't all, man. I got rats and\h
roaches like crips and bloods in my house, man.\h\h
be crawled by shootings all the time. I come\h
home for work out to break up fights. Oh y'all,\h\h
let it go. Let it go. It ain't\h
worth it. Stop that [\h__\h] man. Man,\h\h
they be answering my door. Talking on my phone,\h
won't click over. People done told me a call,\h\h
I ain't heard [\h__\h] from them. That\h
[\h__\h] don't live here. Chris who?
My roach is smart, too, man. They play dead.\h
[laughter] The other day I stepped on one of them,\h\h
went in the bathroom to get some tissue,\h
came back, that [\h__\h] was gone. I seen\h\h
him two weeks later with some stitches.\h
[\h__\h] told me he was too legit to quit.
Man, it's [\h__\h] up when you go in your series to\h\h
get your prize. Them [\h__\h] don't\h
already been in there and got it.
Trip, man. Whatever happened to pimps,\h
man? What if Michael Jackson was a pimp?\h\h
Should be him and Tito be riding\h
around in the Cadillac and [\h__\h]
Slow down, Tito. Slow down,\h\h
Tito. Damn. Is that my ho that's sitting\h
on the curb? Let me out. Come here, girl.
I said, come here, girl. for my money.\h
How much you got? I'm like, I'm sorry.\h\h
All I got is a $100 bill. Girl, you've been out\h
here all day and all you got is a $100 bill.\h\h
[screaming] [cheering] Keep it in the closet.\h
Now get out there and be supported. [cheering]
[cheering] It's [\h__\h] up, man. Ain't nobody\h
high earnest. I'm serious. I know what it is,\h\h
man. White people don't trust black people. That's\h
why they won't vote for no black president. Like\h\h
a black brother will [\h__\h] up the White House\h
like the grass won't be cut. Dishes piled up.\h\h
Cousins running through the White House. Cookouts.\h
Basketball go in the back. Broken down cars. All\h\h
about to [\h__\h] in the driveway. Brother won't\h
clean out the tub when he get out of president\h\h
get pissed off. Somebody done drunk up all the\h
Kool-Aid. Ain't you know a black president,\h\h
man, he too proud. He ain't going to have\h
no bodyguard. A black president, he don't\h\h
have a gun. Somebody fight to [\h__\h] him up. He\h
[\h__\h] him. Hey, [\h__\h] Like, damn. The president\h\h
just [\h__\h] somebody up. You see that [\h__\h]\h
man? My mom threw me out the house, man. Man,\h\h
you ever notice when you're in high school,\h
you your mama's baby, but when you graduate,\h\h
you that [\h__\h] walking around the house?\h
My daddy wanted me to leave all alone,\h\h
man. Leave me little hits and [\h__\h] like\h
leaving army brochures and [\h__\h] on my pillow.\h\h
My mama would do little [\h__\h] like she'll buy\h
peanut butter, went by the jelly, buy Kool-Aid,\h\h
went by sugar. Like, mom, what the [\h__\h] wrong\h
you know? You can't make Kool-Aid without sugar.
[\h__\h] them, man. You can't [\h__\h] no more\h
in your mom's house neither. It's a trip,\h\h
man. Cuz one time, man, I was handling business,\h\h
right? But I had to listen out for my mom. So,\h
I told the girl, I said, "You going to have to\h\h
shut the [\h__\h] up cuz I got to listen up\h
for my mom. I thought I heard something."
Mama don't come home to 6. [cheering]\h
That ain't help. You don't know what\h\h
she's doing. One time my mom's caught me, man.\h
Was [\h__\h] up. I was helling business, right?\h\h
I mean, I was on the floor and the\h
bed was shaking. My mom said, "Chris,\h\h
what you doing?" I said, "Nothing, mama."\h
She said, "Come here, boy." I said, "Mom,\h\h
I'm coming." Said, "Come here, boy." I said, "Mom,\h
I'm coming." Someone hurry up. I said, "I'm trying\h\h
to give you Shut the [\h__\h] up." They got on Chris\h
Tucker. [applause] [music] [cheering] [applause]
[cheering]
Yo, give him another round of applause.\h
[applause] Hey, and the the boy is what?\h\h
What is he? 20 years old. Bad young brother.\h
Give Oh, god damn. Come here, boy. [applause]
All [laughter] right, coming\h
to the stage. It's my man. We\h\h
used to work out a lot in DC. But yo,\h
give it up Kevin Anthony. Give it up.
[cheering]
Y'all in a good mood? Yeah, I'm excited. My\h
woman just left me and she ain't getting paid\h\h
[\h__\h] either. Some of you brothers probably can\h
relate to this. was difficult living with some\h\h
women cuz they started talking [\h__\h] about old\h
boyfriend. My last boyfriend when he lived here,\h\h
he paid the rent, the telephone bill,\h
the car note, brought some food,\h\h
and gave me some money to go out shopping.\h
I said, "Shit, we need to get his ass back\h\h
here." [applause] What's his number? Buy me some\h
[\h__\h] But the ladies of the ' 90s, you're doing\h\h
well for yourselves. Give yourselves a round\h
of applause, ladies. [applause and cheering]
Yeah, you're intelligent. You're into aerobics.\h
You're lifting weights. Women in the fashion.\h\h
David invented names for their underwear. Skinny\h
women call them panties. Heavier women call them\h\h
bloomers. And big fat women, I guess they\h
wrap a sheet around their ass and call it a\h\h
day. But women are very creative with their love\h
making. Cuz one chick say, "Baby, have you ever\h\h
had anybody hum on your balls? No, but go for it.\h
She went, "How you like that?" I said, "You better\h\h
hum another tune." So, she went for the beatbox.\h
I said, "Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Express yourself."
And I'm creative with my love making. I like\h
to do it doggy style. And I don't care who\h\h
you are. If you're in front of a mirror,\h
you going to look. cuz I was getting busy\h\h
one night knocking boots. I'm talking rocking\h
that funky joint. I look in the mirror and go.
[applause] And women just as vain\h
as we are cuz she was like this.\h\h
Back up a little bit. Let me see.\h
Okay, baby. No problem. [applause]
Women name their body parts like men\h
name theirs, right? I call mines the\h\h
beef injector. My mother called my father's\h
the old raisin. Women named theirs, too,\h\h
right? What you call yours, baby? You\h
can't call it is it dead? [applause] I\h\h
asked one chick that I said, "What\h
you call yours, baby?" She said,\h\h
"Terminator." I said, "That's some [\h__\h]\h
you keep. [cheering] I'll be back. [applause]
But women biggest problem with us\h
is the orgasm. Cuz they'll tell you,\h\h
"You come too quick. [\h__\h] You come too\h
late. I've been here two weeks. I have a\h\h
job." And then when they get that orgasm,\h
they act like they've been electrocuted\h\h
or some [\h__\h] They do. You hit them with the\h
wild thing. They're like [cheering] [applause]
And then we get sensitive. Did\h
you come? She said a little bit.\h\h
You guys been great. Love you, New\h
York. Peace. [applause and music]
[music]
That's for me. Oh, thank you. Bring it to me. Come\h
here, girl. Going to give me flowers. Thank you,\h\h
baby. Thank you. So, we [\h__\h] laid on then, man.\h
Thank you, baby. Thank you. No one's ever gave me\h\h
anything. Thank you from Elizabeth, New Jersey.\h
This is my man Alonszo Hamburger Joe [applause]
[cheering] [applause]
[cheering]
[cheering] Hamburg. How you folk feel\h
out here tonight? [cheering] [applause]
Look at this big joke here. Same\h
D stand in front of YMCA about Oh,\h\h
look. They done spelled Macy's wrong.
[cheering]
Hamburg. I ain't going to have it. Who else\h
want to play? Happy Halloween, baby. [cheering]
Hamburg. Check out my man here, Rico Suave. Yeah,\h
I'm looking good out here. H Burger, y'all look at\h\h
it big round away girl like been sitting on a bus\h
stop sucking on pork chops. Hamburg. [cheering]
[cheering] Hamburg. You know I'm telling the\h
truth. [cheering] [applause] Angel witness\h\h
here. Of course not. They home sleeping. So\h
they wake us up tomorrow morning. [applause]
H B. Don't get me wrong. I love religion. I love\h
religion. I go to church whenever I can afford it.\h\h
I went to church last Sunday. They\h
had five collections. You hear me?\h\h
H burger. Five collections. And that was\h
just in the damn parking lot. [laughter]
Get inside the church. They got a Mac machine in\h
the lobby. [laughter] [cheering] Take another two\h\h
steps. Usher sitting there with a metal detector\h
running up down people. I said, "What's the\h\h
matter? You got a weapons problem in church?" They\h
said, "No, pastor just don't want nobody bringing\h\h
change into the church." I said, "Hamburg, ain't\h
this something?" [applause] And for all this money\h\h
you spend, you think about the world's greatest\h
service. They got some old 90-year-old lady who\h\h
can't read a lick sitting up there trying to\h
read the announcements. Sister Truit going to\h\h
come up there. First giving God, Grand Bishop\h
Johnson, Pastor Me, and friends. [applause]
We the members of Darling Rock Baptist Church\h
would like to thank you for worshiping with us\h\h
this Sunday morning. And now for the\h
announcements. Oh, I'm sorry. That's\h\h
announcements. [cheering] The Kenya choir will be\h
selling dinners $600 each. Oh, Lord. I'm sorry.\h\h
That's going to be $6 each. And we like to thank\h
back to the church, Brother Sister Wilson. Stand\h\h
up, please. Brother Sister Wilson, that newborn\h
baby look just like Pastor Johnson, don't it?
[applause]
I remember one night I took Pork Chop\h
out and see Janet Jackson concert.\h\h
Nice concert. Had words come across\h
the screen. First word came across,\h\h
bigotry. Everybody in the\h
place jumped up and said,\h\h
"No." Next word came across. Man next to me said,\h
"Hey, what's that word?" I said, "Illiteracy."
Oh, no. [cheering]
And I want to tell y'all one\h
thing before I leave here.\h\h
Every time black folk come out with\h
something, white folk got to copy it.
[applause] Pound bird. We came\h
out the Jacksons. They came out\h\h
the Osman's. [laughter] We came out\h
with New Edition. They came out New\h\h
Kids on the Block. [cheering] We came\h
out rap music. They came out MC Hammer.
[cheering]
[cheering]\h\h
Hamburger.
And no matter where I go, folks always\h
say, "Why you say hamburger?" Why do\h\h
you say hamburger? I say hamburger. So I try\h
not to curse. Let me hear everybody here say\h\h
hamburger. Her. No. No. You can say what feel\h
say hamburger. Hamburger. [cheering] Fellas,\h\h
the next time you're in bed with your woman, you\h
get up that good. When she stopped looking at you,\h\h
I want you to look at dead eye and say,\h
"Hamburger." And ladies, don't you feel\h\h
left out cuz hamburger, I got something I want you\h
to say, too. When he stop calling out your name\h\h
and moaning and grown assing, who's is it baby?\h
Who's is it? Who's the best? You look him dead\h\h
in the eye and say, "Ham Vargas, hamburger,\h
you folks been good. Good night. [applause]
[cheering]
[music]
That's my man Alonzo. Give\h
him a round of applause.
[applause]
[\h__\h] that. Don't be saying hamburger\h
when you with your man. Say Mar.
[laughter] All right. Well, coming\h
to the stage is my man. He's been on\h\h
the show before on the Death Jam. So yo,\h
he's from Chicago, Illinois. And uh stand\h\h
like [\h__\h] coffee. Stand like [\h__\h] coffee.\h
Give it up for my man Bernie Mack. [applause]
[cheering]
I ain't scared of you [\h__\h] I'm going\h
to tell you something straight off the\h\h
[\h__\h] press. I ain't coming for no\h
foolishness. and New York. Goddamn it.\h\h
Y'all [\h__\h] women look good. Y'all like\h
a big egg sandwich. You look good cuz I\h\h
love sex. I love it. Can't do [\h__\h]\h
no more. And I'm blessed. [cheering]
I'm big boned. I'm heavy structure.\h
I'm hung low. If I pull my [\h__\h] out,\h\h
this whole room get dark. Kick it. [cheering]
You don't understand. I ain't scared of you [\h__\h]
[cheering] I love I love sex, man. I love\h
it about a pound. I'd be glad they put that\h\h
[\h__\h] in cans. Can you imagine sex in\h
cans? [\h__\h] be shoplifting and [\h__\h]
Folks be playing ball, man.\h
What you getting ready to do,\h\h
man? I'm tired. Give me a six pack\h
of puss. I'm going in. Kick it.
You don't understand. [cheering]
[cheering] [applause] I ain't scared of you [\h__\h]\h
Women just do anything till you talk to any kind\h\h
of way you want to talk to somebody. It don't make\h
no [\h__\h] sense. I'm in a bar minding my business,\h\h
cooling out, just being cool like I am, chilling.\h
Woman going to come to me think she ask any\h\h
goddamn thing she want to do. She said, "Matt," I\h
said, "Yeah, that's my name." Said, "Can I ask you\h\h
a question?" I said, "Yeah." She says, "Does\h
this [\h__\h] taste like pumpkin pie?" Made me\h\h
mad as hell. Don't ask me no damn question like\h
that. I ain't never had no pumpkin pie. Kick it.
You don't understand.
[cheering]
tired of this [\h__\h]
I ain't scared of you [\h__\h]
When you make love to a black woman,\h\h
I'm going to tell you how you do it. You got\h
to be good. I'm not talking about myself cuz\h\h
you know a [\h__\h] ain't number 50 pumps.\h
Count it if you ain't got nothing to do.
It ain't number five minutes, but the foreplay\h
make it seem longer. But you get a woman,\h\h
black woman, man, I'm going to tell\h
you something. I don't care how meek\h\h
that woman is, how soft spoken she\h
is. If you're giving her the dick,
what'sever wrong with you, she going to let\h
you know. You can have a patch on your eye,\h\h
your leg could be broke. If you get up\h
there, she'll be like, "Woo!" [\h__\h]\h\h
You patch eye [\h__\h] You broke leg son of a [\h__\h]\h
You know you in this [\h__\h] Kick ass. [cheering]
You don't understand. God.
[cheering]
And you know what's funny? When you make love\h
to a woman and she on top and the phone ring,\h\h
that's some funny [\h__\h]\h
When she on the phone ring,\h\h
man, every time she on the phone be ring\h
ring, ring, you get cool and [\h__\h] Ring,\h\h
baby don't answer. Ring, I got to answer,\h
baby don't answer. Ringh, it might be a job.
And every time, you know, she pick up the\h
phone, start fiddle fouling with, you know,\h\h
when she pick it up, every time she start to\h
talk, give her the dick. She'll be like, "W
what what what
[cheering] I'm doing this one. You\h
get what I'm doing? Oh, nothing.
[cheering]
But I love my black peoples. I'm going to tell\h
you something. But we got to stop the violence.\h\h
We got to vote. Stop the violence and vote. Cuz\h
I did a show in Chicago. [applause] I mean that.\h\h
Stop this violence. I was in Chicago. I did\h
a show for Cook County Jail and you know over\h\h
40% of the brothers in jail for nothing and\h
they had a little survey little panel thing.\h\h
We got to ask the inmates question you know.\h
So I asked the inmate I said uh hey my brother\h\h
what you in for? He said nothing [laughter]\h
brothers got this thing about being a punk.\h\h
What is a punk? I never did understand that for\h
the sake of my life. He said nothing. I said how\h\h
long you for? He said ever. Now you know it's\h
a long time you take the four off that [\h__\h]
I said, "Man," I said, "So what you for?" I\h
You know, I ain't no punk. I didn't tell on\h\h
my boy. I said, "What? You in jail for a n\h
motherfucker?" "No, you ain't no punk. You a\h\h
new fool cuz I'd be dead if I serve time for any\h
of you [\h__\h] I'll be in court just like this."
Judge be like, "Who are you?" be like,\h
"Punk Jana, he killed that [\h__\h] Shot\h\h
him in the head four times, kicked\h
him in the face. I tried to call you,\h\h
but the line was missing. I'm burning\h
back. I'm out of here. [cheering]
[applause]
Kick it. Get [\h__\h] Get around. Give him a\h
round of applause. God damn it. [cheering]\h\h
[applause] Another one. Bernie Mack. Bernie\h
Mack. Chicago, Illinois. Bernie Mack. Yo,\h\h
I want to thank all of you guys for coming out.\h
Let me holl at my partner who made it possible,\h\h
Russell Simmons. What you got to say? Thanks a\h
lot, y'all. God bless you. Good night. [applause]
[cheering]
Woo! [cheering]